she will say the meanest stuff to me but
i can't break up with her because i'm
not going back to the gym
do you have any single people here any
single ladies in the house
are you single no do any single ladies
single ladies in house
any single ladies gotta have one one
over there what's your name young lady
ariel well that's part of it i uh
you're dating a fish no no she's a
person everybody calm
down all right her name's ariel ariel
what do you look for in a guy first
thing to look for in a guy ariel
you should how are you still single i
don't know
everybody here has something i'm leaving
that's good though stay single it's nice
yeah right you don't need them right do
we have any single guys here any single
guys
single gentlemen anybody
what are some guys at single right here
single what's your name buddy
you're jake shocking you look like a
jake if i were to guess
does this guy not look like the
wikipedia version of jake
if there was ever a jake it would be you
this guy looks like the boise state
quarterback over here jake over here
just
catch the ball please
jake what do you look for in a young
lady jake
kind
no you're a liar jake you don't look for
kindness jake
[Music]
i found somebody with nothing i found
somebody jake's over here
he's got nothing
[Applause]
ariel right here found jake let me know
if you
if you want to go hiking or something
jake's over there
i'll bring snacks i want nothing
i want you to show up with nothing jake
stay single bro it's way easier man are
you guys dating over here dating
married ugh could you imagine
how guys married for 12 years how'd you
guys mean
through friends white people stuff all
right no big deal
only white people have friends by the
way nobody else
i have a girlfriend now it's awful we've
been out for four years we
hate each other she will say the meanest
stuff to me but i can't break up with
her because i'm not going back to the
gym
they're running in there jake
[Music]
my girlfriend and i we just went on
vacation together we got in this huge
fight in the hotel room she won a level
three flip out ladies you know what that
is yelling crying
throwing stuff in the hotel room she
starts threatening me she's like i'm
gonna jump out the window
she's like i'm gonna jump out the window
because the way you make me feel i hate
you i was like oh
snap i panicked i run downstairs i wake
up the manager i'm like hey man wake up
be my girlfriend who's got this huge
fight
he's like that's not my problem if the
look man i don't think you get it she
wants to jump out the window she's going
nuts i need your help
he's like that's not my problem i was
like it is your problem
the window is stuck
this is my only way out sir
just go up there
we both decided to have a hall pass i
know you guys know what a hall pass is
for somebody to know what a hall pass is
we're both allowed to pick one person
that will allow to hook up with if we
ever get the opportunity to meet usually
a celebrity
and the other person can't get mad at
them so my girlfriend picked
the uh the actor from um aquaman
jay i don't i did i ask for his name
did i ask for his name
i don't like him i looked him up very
very handsome
and i saw his girlfriend and she was
super hot so i was like good luck with
that
i don't think it's happening
i have jake's number do you want to call
jake
are you kind
because that's not a kind answer
she's like whatever jerk who's your hall
pass i was like my hall pass is
elizabeth
from applebee's
i'm not gonna waste my hall pass that
would be stupid
she's right over there
i know our schedule like the back of my
hand
[Applause]
good luck deep sea diving for this dude
say hi to ariel while you're down there
i have to keep my girlfriend because
i'll never find another girlfriend i'm
terrible at dates i always try to say
funny stuff
all funny stuff all the time i have no
filter
like i remember the last day i was on is
this woman she started opening up
right like not in a good way emotionally
in a very unkind way
[Music]
she's like you know when i was eight
years old my dad went out to get
hamburgers for the whole family and
never came back and i was like oh mike
those must have been some amazing
hamburgers
do you remember where he went
i want some did he help it we should
find your father could you imagine a
hamburger so good where you just leave
your family
you just take one bite i'm not going
back
i won't go back you gotta go back
what about your kids
my parents want me to get an arranged
marriage
yeah for some of you guys that don't
know what an arranged marriage is that's
in my culture where a guy's dad will
call the girl's parents and they'll just
get them married
without even meeting i thought that was
an awful idea until i saw my cousin's
wife
wow she is super hot
my cousin looks like something out of
narnia
i saw them together i was like uh sign
me up
dude like what a ring think about how
cool could be in america right think
about okube single guys think about it
you're at a club you have the hottest
girl in the club you're like hey baby
you want to dance she's like ah
no then you could say ah well too bad my
dad talked to your dad and guess what
we're dancing
i'm kind
don't try that by the way don't you do
it my best friend is white he always
tries to categorize me recently was like
hey uh hey man you're indian right i'm
like that's right
so you're from india i was like way to
go steve you nailed it
he's all right india's in asia i guess
that makes you asian
i was like nah man asians are chinese
japanese vietnamese all the nieces
it's like my bad you're not asian i
guess it makes you what like middle
eastern right i'm like whoa whoa whoa
asian it is take it easy buddy
don't start that again am i right
do we have any middle easterners here
tonight yeah
all right looks like i'm skipping the
next joke right
how to make sure
it only takes one all right jk
jk everybody
[Music]
i like this i feel at
home i like it
racism goes all the way though like you
know people go listen
white people you know there's a lot of
racism against white people too right
have you seen these documentaries on
serial killers my god
every episode oh no
that's no good everyone
i back you up i got your back i'm like
you know this is racist not all
white people are serial killers
the problem is all serial killers are
white
and that's as far as i can go
what else can i do
and it's not like it's white people's
fault it's not like in your blood it's
just white people only people in the
world that can be serial killers
why you're the only people in the world
that can get away with eight unsolved
murders in a row there's no other
ethnicity that can do that
it's not your fault this is you're the
only one that can do it
so why not
you don't think black people want to be
serials of course they do
they can't
could you imagine a black spirit he
would get pulled over on the way to
getting supplies
he'll just be driving minding your own
business
what seems to be the problem officer
your tail is out no it's not officer
down
i mean is that
indians hispanics asians we can't be
serial killers
our family's way too nosy
my mom's a snitch
my mom would sniff that out
it is a rope what happened in the duct
tape it is a bleach damn mom
get out of my room
i'm checking your trunk you can't go in
the truck mom there's people in there
why are you doing this you raised
me
i'm trying to make a name for myself
that's what you wanted right mother
my mom hates me
i have two sisters one's a doctor one's
a lawyer and i'm this
i'm doing dry bar comedy my mom hates me
my mom's favorite day of the year is
halloween because for one day a year her
son's a doctor
which is very mean my mom said nah dude
every time i upset her she makes me do
weird stuff like a punishment that i
don't even see coming until it happens
last year she made me take my cousin
trick-or-treating for halloween
i was like of course i will i don't care
i love halloween let's go
i'll go pick up my cousin 11 year old
indian kid you know what he's dressed
like
a slurpee
us i wanted to knock the straw off his
head i'm like why
are you dressed like a slurpee you're
indian
people make fun of us about this why
would you decide to dress yourself up
like a slurpee
but i couldn't say any of that because i
was dressed like aladdin
i could say nothing
i was like just hop on the carpet it's
gonna be a long ride
it's the worst
my mom's the boss of my family though i
can't say no to her my mom is
my dad
i didn't realize how useless my dad was
until i was eight years old when i asked
him for some permission he apparently
had no authority of giving me
while my mom was out of the house at
grocery shopping right
i'm eight years old dude i go up to my
dad i'm like hey dad can i go play into
sprinklers
he's like you want to go play into
sprinklers buddy you go ahead
you have a good time don't you buddy
buddy don't you buddy
[Laughter]
i was like i wasn't worried until you
said that three times father
but now i'm very worried thank you
five minutes later i'm the sprinklers
having the time of my life and then
guess who shows up
i don't know or my mom like a falcon she
just lands at a sidewalk piss
she just shows up she's like hey what do
you think you're doing
i was like i'm playing in a sprinkler
she's like who told you
point them out who told you
i would like to meet the person that
told you
i just want to say hello to the person
that said it was okay to play in the
sprinklers can i meet him please can i
please
i'm like mom dad told me i could play
into sprinkles relax she's like oh
you asked your father for permission you
might as well have asked a banana
a banana bro
and then my dad sells me out cause he's
scared of my mom right she's like did
you tell him he could play into
sprinklers he's like i don't even
know this guy
who is this guy i'm like
it's your son father
[Laughter]
of course my mom just learned how to
start text messaging people and by
people i mean me
my mom text messages me the most useless
text messages in the history of text
messages
i got one from her the other day i swear
to you this is what it said verbatim
i whip it out it says oh my god the
remote is not working
it goes on same text same thread i think
it is broken better oh
wait never mind i have fixed it don't
you buddy buddy don't you buddy i'm like
mom
i come home like why would you send this
after you fix the remote
why does your text messages have indian
accents
i don't like any of this
she's a sweetheart
i love doing stand-up comedy this is my
favorite thing to do
all comics are we're all broke not me
i'm doing okay but most comics are broke
they're just fine don't you worry buddy
but i do like being broke though you
know it's fun being rich is boring when
you're broke
every day's an adventure i like it right
when you're broke every day you wake up
you're like if anything happens i'm done
it's like a video game
okay get the thursday follow me i've
been there let's go
i checked the mail the other day i got a
bill it said final notice on it i was
like
thank god
looks like i won't have to deal with
this anymore right wow
i was getting very worried
i win
[Laughter]
it's tough to pay bills even if you have
money there are too many passwords
how are we supposed to remember this i'm
a person not a cloud
i got the verizon bill last week i gotta
crack the davinci code to pay this it
took too long
that was gonna take two minutes i called
on like what's up verizon it's me kabir
sing let's do this
they're like what's your account number
i'm like four seven eight nine four
three two
where do you live 2000 walnut avenue
what's your date of birth 12 30 84 now
what let's go
he's like what's your bill pay password
i was like you bastard
i built
i don't know what that is this should
have been the first question am i right
i don't know what that is please let me
just pay this please please
he's like i can't i need your bill pay
password but i have good news for you in
case you forgot you set up a password
hint
so of course i did i'm always one step
ahead of the game homie
how dare you what's my hints he's like
your hint is turtles
i was like oh no
i was like i don't know any turtles
i've never seen a turtle sir
please let me just pay this so we can
move on with our lives please
he's like i can't i need your bill pay
password i need to make sure it's you
i'm like who is out there paying other
people's bills
nobody steals some dude's identity and
goes up to your friends like let's pay
all the stuff off that doesn't happen
it's the opposite
he's like please let me just pay this
you know what my password turned out to
be it turned out to be rocket
because turtles are slow and rockets are
fast
[Music]
thank you jack daniels and marijuana for
that combination
[Laughter]
what normal person would do that i got
the new iphone with siri on it you guys
have siri
serious racist theory only to understand
why people that's why you only see why
people
use siri on commercials every commercial
why people be
siri could you tell michael and jason
that me and ben are on the way please
bp messes
then i use it with my indian cousin's
names and all hell breaks loose right
and i use it i'm like siri could you
tell rod jinder pretender and sit tinder
that me and priya are on the way please
we located five seven elevens in your
area i'm like why
we made you
traitor i won't stand for it
indians get made in funder for a lot of
stuff too some stuff is true right like
indians will bargain i don't even know
this indians will bargain anytime
anywhere
we'll bargain while we're getting robbed
robbed i've seen it hey put your hands
up okay buddy hear me out
how about i put one hand up okay
everybody calm down
it's like how about i shoot you in the
face how about you just stab me in v
caller today okay
just give me all your stuff how about i
give you half my stuff
and you give me your watch it's a very
good deal you're not calm
that's why you never see any indians on
deal or no deal it would take too long
it would just be four hours some indian
guy yelling no
neil no thank you
it's like we haven't even offered you
anything yet sir you're in line
i actually had the opportunity to do
shows in india which was a blast i don't
know if you know this but we don't use
toilet paper in india did you guys know
that
no we use water in our hands because we
believe that's more
uh hygienic and uh better for the
environment
which is fine with me but the problem is
they told me this eight days into the
trip after i
high-fived half of new delhi i was like
when
no wonder
that was me
my cousin was pumped to see me though he
wanted to impress me the first place he
took me to was an amusement park that
sounds like fun right
roller coasters in a third world country
[Laughter]
i'm already afraid of heights now i'm on
a wooden roller coaster in bangladesh
i'm just going up this like i'm going to
die there's no way i'm going to survive
this
my cousin looks at me it's like don't
buddy buddy these roller coasters are
just like the ones
in america don't you buddy buddy don't
you buddy
okay like hi cool
i look down i see two indians pulling a
rope
one of them gave me a thumbs up i'm like
put your hand back in the road bro
there's people up here
and then i thought to myself wow that
rope must smell like poop
i wouldn't touch that rope
no i'm glad i'm not single dude it's
rough it's rough out there dating
i used to hit on white girls all the
time you guys are the worst
why girl's gonna be super racist
remember last time i was hitting on a
white girl she was like hey you want to
go back to my place i was like hell yeah
i go back to her place jimmy fixed the
computer while she passed out on the
couch
it's not nice
i've also i've actually always wanted a
latina girlfriend do we latinas in house
latin
i love latina i've always wanted a
latina girlfriend i'm just not ready to
start a family
i think this has gone very well
dry bar that's been my time my name is
kabir singh was a privilege and
honorable boy for you guys thank you so
much
i love you guys thank you guys
that means a lot guys hopefully i'll see
you guys in the future
you